Guide to the Kenneth Roman Papers, 1906-2011 and undated RL.01105
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1935-2011 and undated
  - Interview cassettes
    - Clark, Jean. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Clopet, Julian. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Dawson, Michael. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - De Haes, Charles. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2003 (Box 21)
    - DeKay, Helen. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Drake, Burtch. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Elliott, Elly. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Evans, Nick. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Fine, Jules. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 1997 (Box 21)
    - Fine, Jules Continued. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 1997 (Box 21)
    - Fisher, Annie & Alan, undated. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. (Box 21)
    - Fletcher, Winston. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Fowler, Richard. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Fredricks, Charlie. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Gerstner, Lou. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Gregson, Gene. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Guariglia, Chuck. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Harris, Lou. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Hayden, Steve. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2007 (Box 21)
    - Heekin, Jim. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Irish, Jud. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 1999 (Box 21)
    - Kapur, Ranjan and Winter, Roger (Tape 1). Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Kapur, Ranjan and Winter, Roger (Tape 2). Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Keown, Ian. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Korda, Reva and Bill. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 1998 (Box 21)
    - Kummel, Gene. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Kuperma, Bob. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Lauterborn, Bob. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Lazarus, Shelley. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Leszt, Gerry. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Lindsay, Mary. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Lord, Dick. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Maas, Jane and Jones, Abe. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Mayer, Martin. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2007 (Box 21)
    - McCabe, Ed. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - McGee, Jerry. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Morris, Edmund. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Nettleton, John. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Ney, Ed. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2004 (Box 21)
    - Ogilvy, Herta. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Page, Shelby. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Papert, Fred. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Phillips, Bill. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 1997 (Box 21)
    - Phillips, Bill. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Phillips, Graham. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Pickholz, Jerry. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Pitcher, Archie. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Prince Phillip on WWF. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 1998 (Box 21)
    - Putter, Robyn. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2007 (Box 21)
    - Raphaelson, Joel & Marikay. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 1997 (Box 21)
    - Reinhard. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Reiss, Elaine. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Richey-Rankin, Vel. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Rothenberg, Randy. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Ryan, Brendan. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Schultz, Nancy. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Sidnar, Gloria. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Stanton, Frank. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 1998 (Box 21)
    - Stauderman, Bruce. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Stevenson, William. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Stewart, Mac. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Straiton, John. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Tennant, Anthony. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Tiger, Francois/Simone. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Treneman, John/Jill. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Trevellyan, Sheila. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Turner, Mike. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Vaessen, Emile. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Walsh, Mike. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Warren, Peter. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Warren, Peter/Susan. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Weed, Bill. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Wilkie. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2006 (Box 21)
    - Williams, John. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. 2007 (Box 21)
    - Wilson, Lorna, undated. Cassette. TRT: 90.00. (Box 21)
  - Other Audiovisual Materials
    - David Ogilvy Images, undated. CD-R. (Box 22)
    - David Ogilvy Retrospective Radio 4 - UK, Sept. 4, 2000. Ogilvy & Mather. CD-R. 2006 (Box 22)
    - D. Ogilvy Work --Rolls Royce, Hathaway, undated. CD-R. (Box 22)
    - Ogilvy & Mather Hotel Intercontinental (Disc 1 of 2) 1989. Ogilvy & Mather. CD-R. 2011 (Box 22)
    - Ogilvy & Mather Hotel Intercontinental (Disc 2 of 2) 1989. Ogilvy & Mather. CD-R. 2011 (Box 22)
    - Touffou Photos, undated. CD-R. (Box 22)
    - David Ogilvy Advertising Research Foundation, 1994. Ogilvy & Mather. DVD. 2011 (Box 22)
    - David Ogilvy MPEG Files Audio Files, undated. DVD. (Box 22)
    - David Ogilvy on Training, undated. Ogilvy & Mather. DVD. 2011 (Box 22)
    - David Ogilvy: Original Mad Man. Ogilvy Entertainment. DVD. 2008 (Box 22)
    - David Ogilvy Project--The View From Touffou. Ogilvy & Mather. DVD. 2010 (Box 22)
    - David Ogilvy "We Sell or Else" ANA Annual Conference 1991. Ogilvy & Mather. DVD. 2011 (Box 22)
    - David Ogilvy Worldwide Meeting October 1989. Ogilvy & Mather. DVD. 2010 (Box 22)
    - Lord Peter Wimsey Murder Must Advertise Parts (1 & 2). DVD. 1973 (Box 22)
    - Lord Peter Wimsey Murder Must Advertise Parts (3 & 4). DVD. 1973 (Box 22)
    - Rosser Reeves Testimonial, undated. DVD. (Box 22)
    - David Ogilvy work, undated. DVD. (Box 22)
    - Conversations with an Advertising Man by Guy Shahar, undated. DVD. TRT: (Box 22)
    - A Conversation About Advertising with David Ogilvy. A.A.A.A. VHS. TRT: 60:00. (Box 23)
    - Advertising On Ogilvy. Ogilvy & Mather. VHS. TRT: 22:18. 1997 (Box 23)
    - O & M Officers Meeting: Ken Roman and Martin Sorrell. Ogilvy & Mather. VHS. TRT: 60:00. 1989 (Box 23)
    - O & M Worldwide Management Meetings: David Ogilvy Speech. Ogilvy & Mather. VHS. TRT: 30:00. 1989 (Box 23)
    - Ruggles of Red Gap. Paramount Productions/MCA Universal. VHS. TRT: 90.00. 1935 (Box 23)
    - Sell & Spin: A History of Advertising: Acts 5-8. The History Channel. VHS. TRT: 49:45. 1999 (Box 23)
    - View From Touffou, undated. VHS. TRT: 38:00. (Box 23)
    - Leo Burnett--When To Take My Name Off the Door, undated. Leo Burnett Company, Inc. VHS. TRT: 15:00. (Box 23)
    - Witness. Paramount Productions/MCA Universal. VHS. TRT: 112:00. 1985 (Box 23)